{
    "subject": "resource/Herchweiler",
    "predicate": "ontology/district",
    "object": "resource/Kusel_(district)",
    "human_readable": "Herchweiler is in the district of Kusel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8529060482978821,
            "question": "What is the significance of Herchweiler within the context of Kusel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7395994067192078,
            "question": "What district does Herchweiler belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114291191101074,
            "question": "Where is Herchweiler located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5707014203071594,
            "question": "In which region is Kusel situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5259296298027039,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the district of Kusel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48870548605918884,
            "question": "Is there any historical information associated with Herchweiler and its location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47631996870040894,
            "question": "Are there any notable places or landmarks in Herchweiler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32812967896461487,
            "question": "How would you describe the geographical features surrounding Herchweiler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3072700500488281,
            "question": "What are some of the local industries or economic activities in Herchweiler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27723029255867004,
            "question": "Are there any cultural events or festivals celebrated in Herchweiler?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Herchweiler is in the district of Kusel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3833_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the local industries or economic activities in Herchweiler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3833_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the geographical features surrounding Herchweiler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3833_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable places or landmarks in Herchweiler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3833_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3833_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Herchweiler is in the district of Kusel. The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3833/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt states \"Welcome to Herchweiler, a charming village in the district of Kusel, Germany.\" This directly supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}